# Each open ended question is a dictionary, containing three items:
# question: (str) Question Text
# answer: (str) The correct answer. Case Insensitive.

questions = [
    {"question": "Grumpy is an SUTD animal. What is she?", "answer": "Cat"},
    {
        "question": "Where was SUTD's temporary campus before the Upper Changi Campus opened?",
        "answer": "Dover",
    },
    {
        "question": "A giant pokemon sculpture used to sit in various places in SUTD. Which pokemon?",
        "answer": "Snorlax",
    },
    {
        "question": "How many ceiling fans are there in the campus centre?",
        "answer": "5",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the establishment that used to occupy D'star Bistro?",
        "answer": "Cake Shop",
    },
    {
        "question": "The direct underground entrance to Upper Changi MRT (beside Crooked Cooks) opened in the year:",
        "answer": "2019",
    },
    {"question": "When did SUTD end its collaboration with MIT?", "answer": "2017"},
    {
        "question": """The "Chinese Structure" in hostel grounds is donated by a famous movie actor:""",
        "answer": "Jackie Chan",
    },
    {
        "question": "In the old days freshmore students used to build cannons to launch projectiles into NUS as part of their physics 1D project. What projectile was fired?",
        "answer": "Potato",
    },
    {
        "question": """In outreach workshops, the Office of Marketing often sells the "hacker culture" in SUTD by showing a historical photograph of students placing a certain object on the root. What was it?""",
        "answer": "Police Car",
    },
    {'question': 'Before the current SUTD Hostel, student housing was done differently. What was this Housing programme called?', 'answer': '6ixdegrees'},
    {'question': "During the 10 years' anniversary event, Marketing deployed a piloted robot carrying rings that would light up a sculpture. What is the sculpture of?", 'answer': 'Tree'},
    {'question': 'For the launch of SUTD Academy, there was a car model placed on the pedestal which had a car model number on its side. What is this model number?', 'answer': 'X18'}, 
    {'question': 'Where is the first campus of SUTD located?', 'answer': 'Commonwealth'},
    {'question': 'There are two things referred to as "SAC" in SUTD; one of them is a council. The other is a __?', 'answer': 'Room'},
    {'question': 'There is a light water vehicle with pontoons under the stairs at building 2, made for a competition. What was this competition?', 'answer': 'RobotX'},
    {'question': "SUTD's Architecture and Sustainable Design has traditionally helped out with an installation for a specific holiday. Which holiday is this?", 'answer': 'Chinese New Year'},
    {'question': 'How many crossings, not including the ground floor, go between two separate school buildings in SUTD (as of 2020)?', 'answer': '5'}
]
